<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VPN kill switch</title>
    <link>https://vpn-kill-switch.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on VPN kill switch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright> </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 13:18:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vpn-kill-switch.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How it works</title>
      <link>https://vpn-kill-switch.com/post/how-it-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 13:18:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vpn-kill-switch.com/post/how-it-works/</guid>
      <description>killswitch, in a nutshell, once enabled, it will allow only traffic within the VPN, if the VPN goes down or it crashes, your traffic / IP address will not become exposed.
Before enabling the kill switch killswitch -e the VPN needs to be up and running.
By just running killswitch, information about the existing interfaces and public IP address is printed. Example:
$ killswitch Interface MAC address IP en1 ac:21:37:b1:81:b4 192.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install killswitch</title>
      <link>https://vpn-kill-switch.com/post/killswitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 21:15:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vpn-kill-switch.com/post/killswitch/</guid>
      <description>killswitch a CLI tool for creating &amp;amp; loading pf rules.
To install on Mac OS X:
$ brew tap vpn-kill-switch/killswitch  Next:
$ brew install killswitch  Download from https://dl.bintray.com/nbari/killswitch/ or compile from source: https://github.com/vpn-kill-switch/killswitch
killswitch helps to find the active interfaces and creates a .killswitch.pf.conf file.
Automatically will try to find your VPN peer endpoint IP or you can specify the VPN endpoint IP by using the option -ip</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PF macOS &amp; BSD</title>
      <link>https://vpn-kill-switch.com/post/pf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 16:24:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vpn-kill-switch.com/post/pf/</guid>
      <description>For Mac OS X &amp;amp; BSD users PF can be the best option to create a kill switch.
 PF (Packet Filter, also written pf) is a BSD licensed stateful packet filter, a central piece of software for firewalling. It is comparable to netfilter (iptables), ipfw and ipfilter. PF was developed for OpenBSD, but has been ported to many other operating systems. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/PF_(firewall)
 To create a kill switch using PF, a configuration file</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://vpn-kill-switch.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 15:19:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vpn-kill-switch.com/about/</guid>
      <description>What is a VPN kill switch?  A kill switch, also known as an emergency stop or e-stop, is a safety mechanism used to shut off a device or machinery in an emergency situation in which it cannot be shut down in the usual manner. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kill_switch
 A VPN Kill-Switch is a critical piece of your VPN security solution. Also known as an Internet Kill Switch, this will make sure that your true IP address is never exposed online in the event of a dropped VPN connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vpn-kill-switch.com/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vpn-kill-switch.com/readme/</guid>
      <description>How to contribute You can contribute in multiple ways, submiting code, creating and update existing posts, etc.
Creating &amp;amp; updating posts You can clone the full site by doing this:
First install HUGO: https://gohugo.io/overview/installing/
$ brew update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; brew install hugo  Clone the template repository:
$ git clone git@github.com:vpn-kill-switch/template.git $HOME/vpn-kill-switch.com  Clone the content for the site as a submodule:
$ cd $HOME/vpn-kill-switch.com $ git submodule add -b master git@github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>